<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety.feature"
      label="Safety Annex"
      version="1.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="University of Minnesota Critical Systems Group">

   <description url="">
      Tools developed under the AMASE project: 
         The Safety Annex for the Architecture Analysis and Design Language (AADL) 
         provides the ability to reason about faults and faulty component behaviors in AADL models. 
         In the Safety Annex approach, we use formal assume-guarantee contracts to define the 
         nominal behavior of system components. The nominal model is then verified using the 
         Assume Guarantee Reasoning Environment (AGREE). The Safety Annex provides a way to 
         weave faults into the nominal system model and analyze the behavior of the system in 
         the presence of faults. The Safety Annex also provides a library of common fault node 
         definitions that is customizable to the needs of system and safety engineers.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2017, UMN All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      Copyright (c) 2017, UMN All rights reserved.
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
      documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    * Neither the name of UMN nor the
      names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
      derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL UMN BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <includes
         id="com.rockwellcollins.atc.agree.feature"
         version="2.5.2"/>

   <includes
         id="com.collins.trustedsystems.z3.feature"
         version="4.7.1"/>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety"/>
      <import plugin="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety.analysis"/>
      <import plugin="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtend"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext"/>
      <import feature="com.rockwellcollins.atc.agree.feature" version="2.5.1.qualifier"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety.analysis"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.umn.cs.crisys.safety.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
